TINA STULL: Hi.
I'm Tina Stull, and I drive the Top Dragster for Interstate Batteries.
During this time, it's the time that you check your tire pressure, you might want to walk up and watch the light a little bit.
In Super Comp, we have upwards of a hundred plus cars in an event.
So, usually, unless you got there at the very front of the pack, you're going to be standing around a bit.
So, you can get a little bit acclimated, see how you're going to be able to turn into that lane.
Some of--all the tracks are different so sometimes you get a straight shot and it's no problem.
Sometimes you have to make turns and just kind of watching the cars ahead of you so you don't end up by having to back up and get embarrassed over that.
Then, once you see the guys, pretty much watch the people in front of you; when they start suiting up and hopping in their cars, that's probably the time for you to hop in your car.
Make sure you have all your safety equipment before you leave the pit and you're on your way.